/*quiz_data10 */

const questions = [
    {
//817問目
question:"express(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["表現する、伝える","釈放する","税金","気の毒に思う"],
correctAnswer: "表現する、伝える"
    },
    {
//824問目
question:"trip(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["疑う","経済","はっきりと","旅"],
correctAnswer: "旅"
    },
    {
//833問目
question:"touch(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["口論","寝る","申し込む","触る"],
correctAnswer: "触る"
    },
    {
//842問目
question:"tend(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["投資","利点","裁判所","傾向がある"],
correctAnswer: "傾向がある"
    },
    {
//849問目
question:"match(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["匹敵する","そのように","準備ができている","比べる"],
correctAnswer: "匹敵する"
    },
    {
//874問目
question:"competition(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["国際的な","得る","警察","競争"],
correctAnswer: "競争"
    },
    {
//885問目
question:"obviously(副詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["明らかに","中くらい","速く","材料"],
correctAnswer: "明らかに"
    },
    {
//896問目
question:"throughout(前置詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["まとめる","歌う","～にわたって、～を通じて","貧しい"],
correctAnswer: "～にわたって、～を通じて"
    },
    {
//900問目
question:"guess(動詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["推測する","仕事","触る","忘れる"],
correctAnswer: "推測する"
    },
    {
//997問目
question:"estimate(名詞)の意味は？",
choices: ["単独","資金","瞬間","予算"],
correctAnswer: "予算"
    }
];

export default questions;

